Donald Hopkins

123 Your Street, Boston, MA 12345 dhopkins@exarnple.com (123) 456-7890

A recent graduate with a master's degree in theology, specializing in community outreach, spiritual development, youth ministry, and preaching. A proven track record of supporting volunteer and charity initiatives to aid the local community.

Key Skills

- Theology
- Public Ministry
- Pastoral Teaching
- Community Outreach
- ♦ Spiritual Development
- Youth Ministry

Professional Experience

Ministry Volunteer

Teen Challenge, Boston, MA j May 2020 - Present

- Provide youth ministry services to teenagers and adults suffering from behavioral and substance abuse issues
- Deliver pastoral counseling and teach Bible classes to facilitate the spiritual and personal growth of program members
- Coordinate with counselors, ministers, pastors, and volunteers to plan and execute events and community service initiatives

Volunteer

St. Mary's Lutheran Congregation, Boston, MA j May 2018 - May 2020

- Supported the pastor in providing ministry services to the local congregation, including planning and managing church events to drive community engagement
- Interfaced with the local population and supported outreach initiatives to invite members of the community to join the congregation
- Coordinated with the congregation and minister to execute charity events, including food drives, Toys for Tots, and book fairs

Education

Master of Arts (M.A.) Theology

University Of Boston, Boston, MA September 2019 - September 2021

Bachelor of Arts (M.A.) Religious Studies

University Of Boston, Boston, MA September 2015 - May 2019